<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="jumping_jack">
Start with your feet together and your arms
by your sides,then jump up with your feet apart and
your hands overhead.

Return to the starting position then do the next
rep.This exercise provides a full-body workout and
works all your large muscle
    </string>
    <string name="abdominal">
Lie on your back with your knees bent and your arms
stretched forward. Then lift your upper body off the floor.

Hold for a few seconds and slowly return
It primarily works the rectus abdominus muscle and
the obliques
    </string>
    <string name="plank">
Lie on the floor with your toes and forearms on the ground.

Keep your body straight and hold this position as long as you can.
    </string>
    <string name="push_up">
Lay prone on the ground with arms supporting your body.
Keep your body straight while raising and lowering your
body with your arms.

This exercise works the chest, shoulders, triceps, back and legs.
    </string>
    <string name="step_up">
Stand in front of a chair. Then step up on the chair
and step back down.

The exercise works to strengthen the legs and buttocks
    </string>
   <!--arms-->
    <string name="arms_circle">
Stand on the floor with your arms extended straight out
to the sides at shoulder height.

Move your arms forward in circles, and then move backwards.
    </string>
    <string name="triceps_dips">For the start position, sit on the chair. Then move your hip off
the chair with your hands holding the edge of the chair.

Slowly bend and stretch your arms to make your body go up and down.
This is a great exercise for the triceps
    </string>
    <string name="mountain_climber">
Start in the push-up position. Bend your right knee
towards your chest and keep your left leg straight,
then quickly switch from one leg to other.

This exercise strengthens multiple muscle groups
    </string>
    <!--abs-->
    <string name="sit_ups">
Lie on your back with your hands behind your ears. Then lift your
upper body off the floor and slowly up to the sitting position.
Don’t tug your neck when you get up.

If your spine hurts, please change to another workout.
    </string>
    <string name="leg_raises">
Lie down on your back and put your hands beneath your hips for support.
Then lift your legs up until they form a right angle with the floor.

Slowly bring your legs back down and repeat the exercise.
    </string>
    <string name="russian_twist">
Sit on the floor with your knees bent, feet lifted a little bit
and back tilted backwards.

Then hold your hands together and twist from side to side.
    </string>
    <!--back-->
    <string name="reverse_snow_angels">
Lie face down, extend arms straight overhead, lift arms and legs off the ground,
externally rotate arms in a sweeping motion, engage core muscles, maintain
control, and repeat for desired repetitions.

Reverse snow angels target the back and core muscles, promoting improved posture
and spinal alignment while strengthening the abdominal and lower back muscles.
    </string>
    <string name="superman">
Lie face down on the floor, extend your arms forward, simultaneously lift
your arms and legs off the ground, hold for a few seconds.

while squeezing your glutes and engaging your back muscles, then lower back
down and repeat for desired repetitions to strengthen your posterior
chain and improve core stability.
    </string>
    <string name="hip_hinge">Lie face down on the floor, extend your arms forward, simultaneously
lift your arms and legs off the ground, hold for a few seconds while squeezing
your glutes and engaging your back muscles, then lower back down and repeat
for desired repetitions to strengthen your posterior chain and
improve core stability.
    </string>
    <string name="aqua_man">First lift your right arm and the left leg as much as you can.
And when you bring the two down, lift your left arm and your
right leg. Do both these movements as fast as possible.
    </string>
<!--leg-->
    <string name="cursty_lunges">
Stand straight up. Then step back with your left leg to the right
and bend your knees at the same time.

Go back to the start position and switch to the other side.
    </string>

<string name="pile_squats">
Stand with your hands on your hips and feet a little wider than shoulder width apart.
Then lower your body until your thighs are parallel to the floor.
Your knees should be extended in the same direction as your tiptoes</string>

<string name="side_lying">
Lie down on your side with your head rested on your right arm.
Lift your upper leg up and return to the start position.

Make sure your left leg goes straight and down during the exercise
it is a great exercise for the glutes.
</string>


<string name="bottom_leg">
Lie on your left side with your head resting on your left hand.

Then put your right foot forward on the floor. Lift your left leg up and down.
</string>

    <string name="wall_sit">
Start with your back against the wall, then slide
down until your knees are at a 90-degree angle.

Keep your back against the wall with your hands
and arms away from your legs. Hold the position.
The exercise is to strengthen the quadriceps muscles.
   </string>

</resources>